Guide to the Museum of Biblical Art Records 1997-2015 MS 3094
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Press Clippings, 1998-2015; 4.5 Linear feet
  - Press clippings, February 15-May 26, 2013 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 7)
  - Press clippings, 2011-2013 (3 folders) (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8-10)
  - Media log, August 1998-May 2000 (duplicate), 1998-2000 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 6)
  - Media log, July 2000-August 2001 (duplicate), 2000-2001 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 7)
  - Media log, December 2001-September 2002 (duplicate), 2001-2002 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 8)
  - Press clippings, January-March 2003 (duplicate) (Offsite-box 6, Folder 9)
  - Media log, May 2003-September 2003 (duplicate) (Offsite-box 6, Folder 10)
  - Press clippings, 2011-2013 (duplicate) (3 folders) (Offsite-box 6, Folder 11-13)
  - Additional Excess Copies, 1998-2015 (Offsite-box 30)
- Series IV. Printed Materials, 1998-2015; 1.5 Linear feet
  This series contains programs and brochures created for MoBiA and its projects. These are usually created for each individual exhibition and they include postcards, pamphlets, and leaflets for the visitors of the museum. There are limited items for the earliest exhibitions during the period that MoBiA was the Gallery at the American Bible Society. There may be multiple duplicates for some of the items.
  The materials of this series are arranged in chronological order.
  - Printed materials, 1998-1999 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 11)
  - Printed materials, 1999-2000 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 12)
  - Printed materials, 2001 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 1)
  - Printed materials, 2001-2002 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 2)
  - Printed materials, 2002-2003 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 3)
  - Printed materials, 2003-2004 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 4)
  - Printed materials, 2005 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 5)
  - Printed materials, 2006 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 6)
  - Printed materials, 2007 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 7)
  - Printed materials, 2008 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 8)
  - Printed materials, 2009 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 9)
  - Printed materials, 2010-2011 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 1)
  - Printed materials, 2011-2012 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 2)
  - Printed materials, 2012-2013 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 3)
  - Printed materials (2 folders), 2013-2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 4-5)
  - Additional Excess Copies, 1998-2015 (Offsite-box 30)